I seem to think on my own that the weight
of the sun can be tried again I'll try
anything for you. If you please Dr.
DOCTOR. And I.
Don't know what to point to symbol to
Allegro to QUANTRILL I. Think good you're
supposed to be singing about the
voice of spring not the opposite of
a poppy you know it
with the fruit not like
a bellow. That that you give me the
bed oh.
Well. Play.
Back and we've got enough of the day you
might hurt your voice you know and crack
it up like it or some of them. Don't
forget we've got another man
who is going to gobble with
a whole range of my professors I know you
would want anything to happen to my.
Except to have somebody kind of how
would you like to be married to
a dame like that don't even say that. I
ought to you want to know what I'm going to
be
a little more careful shut up unless you
remember your uncle Caleb do I why don't.
Find spider which you have lost in
a wheel I want to just died and left you
five hundred thousand bucks just like that
old skinflint. I don't it
wasn't by. Fool game like I was
so you was well and good to be sure you
don't get it back again but I want to but
we do but there's one little catch you
get the dope provided you're married to.
MARY No no I'm going to
pay for all our walk
if you get married within forty eight hours
of the reading of the well what time
was that six o'clock and I for less than
an hour to get the bride to be done no
woman who didn't threaten me my. That how
but if you look real hard you might find
one of the men have
a million bucks maybe something they have
done right he had you know he got out I
got
a lot of numbers but I haven't had much
luck with him lately and you can't account
for trying where the phone found all the
time we went back down the line down the
aisle oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh the
nickel make seventeen you want to get
jacked up with want to go ahead.
Gimme some one on it to.
Say they're over an hour
when I get nervous about when him poured
on the charm no danger resist him I hope
you're right I won't be integrating it is
well you little know comes I'm about to
do you
a big favor. Will You
Marry Me Oh all. Right
any luck I've got one fellow number
one nickel and stop using that.
Clumsy way that it would go
to some place I've. Had.
This receiver I got it I got it. All right
you take it away and I'm quite all right
now I get out of here or I.
Don't have what I got here
but all that what about it made the round
up that my arm went up here around the
neck but you're. All right. Of my boy get
All right Lauren Howard it
would I know can you. All
along. If I come around like.
You know if this one was that well we don't
feel a little bit and what I did did
a lightweight. How do. We make
a place. Like I think right
I'd like the Oregon. All
right and they're not
going to vote. Oh well
yeah. I do.
My friends my hand out you're
all right you heard our.
Way Home same it would you like to get
married get married well I don't know but
you are kind of cute at that
oh it's not me and him.
All right I didn't much time left you
know what I don't think. That's what I
want to know. What about.
If you get
a little That's what I want
to. Find out. We do pay. You
back you and good looking to go get
a share. Or. You can propose to
a girl looking like that we've
got to go to work come on.
Stand still why do we gotta get going to
three o'clock not yet you know Maya go by
I think we're out of the
money. I said Stand still.
I'm. Your point why are.
They where other jobs
are all. I've got if.
You look really what up
on the ground all that.
Why are you. Here. Say I forgot to tell
you when the afternoon papers come out
you're going to be famous How come I gave
the story to the reporters yes I am I'll
do it now that I have
a million but let's get going to get. A
Hold Still I want to know
what that's. All say I.
Always had seven years bad luck.
You'll. Feel like that.
I felt they had done oh all.
Right I close my head off
oh I did not I if I did not know.
Oh yeah right here and I'd
Where do you think it may get gone
or may. Not know what I mean.
You know our. Boy might cry
or what's all this water.
Oh. You look good you look
great interested go to.
Hell of
a low level Oh. Well. I'm
happy to see you I just been dying to be
you know. Me But you don't do them good.
Oh boy you didn't. Think
it was just. Kind of.
Oh you must be gone. Let me. Say oh.
Why don't you go why did. I know
what you're talking. You look up
things when really I would if you were
going to buy but they don't think you will
be there to. Get like me you.
Ready for you with that last.
Gap. And I hope
a crying because. You won't. Buy home
all I wanted to do with the problem
would go oh oh. You mean you really
marry Hello caller do you monitor no phone
when you're going to be able to say oh.
Wait a minute we're going
to say when I have
a million bucks we only got two
hours left I'm gonna get on the.
Farm ready to go OK you. Know years
and I didn't want to get married in
a rush Oh it better to. Use me. Hello. Mr
hour you know we've been here.
Oh yes. How many of them
well yeah OK thanks. For the like of the
apartment but we think your phone this
morning found out about five hundred grand
of the papers come on now we've got to
make this fair Have you got the ring
I said I think I think I got to.
Get it. Yeah Wyatt. But you know what
you know I think a piano down to
a guy. I think I think. Like that yeah.
You know I think all of you want to find
my looks impossible but I guess they can
get that right if they
want to sing. Oh I'm
sorry I saw fine. OK when I
run in and get that rain oh
oh oh. Oh
oh oh oh oh oh your kind of up wind
I'll back him up with regular. I
don't. Want to.
Eat away at the oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh get in the messes every time you give
me
a. Few minutes left and no rain no
matter what even if I would. Hear
the rain might get better. OK I know we're
ready for the kick off your mind and
you.
For
a lead character for the burning
hour you know I got my friends and I
mean yes but I will get into.
That if I read the papers that OK
let
a lot of people. Write that we better
do. It Right I don't know what.
I.
Mean I. Don't read your thank.
You. Are my. Eyes.
You wouldn't get away with that.
Thank. You Mary Mary.
Snow. Thank you. Thank.
You.
For.
Oh oh. Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh. Oh oh.
Oh oh what are you.
Saying you were. Oh.
Yeah I mean how am I. To
nation. You have. Made
it in your memory I have a right
to your money can't say something.